wikidownload.com 2019-04-22

# This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which wikiDownload Inc collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://wikidownload.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by wikiDownload Inc.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which wikiDownload Inc collects, uses, maintains and
discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of
the http://wikidownload.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all
products and services offered by wikiDownload Inc.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but
not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other
activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for,
as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will
collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such
information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except
that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with
our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of
computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the
operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on
their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them.
User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are
being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
wikiDownload Inc may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
     •    - To improve customer service
          Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support
          needs more efficiently.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to
protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal
information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share
generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information
regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the
purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our
partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the
content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by

websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and
links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies
and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites
which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set
cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you
an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others
who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver
targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does
not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Google Adsense
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve
ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non
personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as
your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie
by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy
at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Changes to this privacy policy
wikiDownload Inc has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will
post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this
page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal
information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this
privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not
agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the
posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with
this site, please contact us at:
wikiDownload Inc
90 Alton Rd Suite 804 Miami Beach, FL 33139
1(305)600-0125
wikidownload99@gmail.com
This document was last updated on January 20, 2014
Privacy policy created by Generate Privacy Policy
